We're here, Nephrites.
下船咯 涅芙丽缇丝
Wait for me!
等等我
This place is said to be at the edge of the world.
听说这里位于世界的边陲
It's surprisingly bustling.
没想到还满热闹的嘛
The Kingdom of Water, Maasa.
水之国 麻萨
It may be at the border,
虽然位于边境
but this is the most thriving city.
但这里是最繁华的首都
By the way, where is Marse?
话说回来 马尔斯先生呢
He had something to tend to
他好像有什么事
and went on ahead.
所以先走了
I see.
这样啊
He's always wanted to come here.
毕竟他一直很想来水之国
There must be a reason for that.
果然是有什么原因吗
Excuse me!
不好意思
You must be the Ring King, right?
你就是戒王陛下 对吧
Yes.
没错
Wonderful!
太棒了
I'm your biggest fan!
我是你的忠实支持者
Hey, you're embarrassing me.
这样啊 真令人害羞
You're quite popular here.
还真是受欢迎
As expected from my husband.
不愧是我丈夫
Oh, right. Please accept this bouquet.
对了 请收下这束花
And this too.
还有这个
I heard rumours about you,
虽然之前就听过传闻
but you're such a careless fool!
你真是个毫无防备的大蠢蛋
Ring King!
戒王
Huh...
什…
My name is Saphir Maasa.
妾身是瑟菲珞·麻萨
The Ring Princess of Water.
水戒公主
From now on, you are my husband.
从现在开始 你就是我的丈夫了
Is this even allowed?
这样也行吗
Yeah.
行
TALES OF WEDDING RINGS
《婚戒物语》
Thank you for aiding us,
谢谢你果断帮助我们
Ring Princess of Water.
水戒公主
Don't mention it.
不必多礼
You seem pretty calm, Great Sage.
不愧是大贤者 真镇定
As for the others...
至于其他人…
Oh...
哦…
I've met the other princesses, so that's enough.
总之公主们只要打个照面就好
We're not going to be best friends anyway.
反正我们也不会深交
Now, Ring King,
那么 戒王
I've made you my husband.
妾身已经让你成为丈夫
That makes you the king of this country.
你就是这个水之国的国王
I knew it.
果然是这样吗
It's your duty and responsibility to bring stability to this country.
你有责任和义务 让这个国家变安稳
Get ready.
你应该做好心理准备了吧
Yes.
嗯
Come with me.
跟我来吧
Unleash your true potential for me.
为了妾身 充分发挥你的力量
My full potential?
要我发挥力量…
What's going on here?
到底出了什么事
At this rate, the country is going to be destroyed.
再这样下去 这个国家会灭亡
Here you are,
原来您在这种地方啊
Princess Saphir.
瑟菲珞公主
Please return to the palace.
请您回王宫
This is the Ring King.
这位是戒王
I just made him my husband
他刚刚被我选为丈夫
and gave him Maasa's Ring of Water.
把麻萨的水之戒交给他了
Will there be a problem?
应该没什么问题吧
Understood.
我明白了
Please follow us to the palace.
请各位先到王宫来吧
That is huge!
好壮观
The great waterfall El-Wuyo Massa.
那是大瀑布艾乌尤麻萨
An iconic landmark of this country.
可以说是水之国麻萨的地标
The old Kingdom of Earth is just past that waterfall.
越过那道瀑布就是以前的土之国
It's also known as the Dark Domain, where the Abyss King resides.
也被称为深渊王躲藏的黑暗领域
Look.
你们看
The empire's soldiers are everywhere.
城里到处都是帝国的士兵
Maasa no long has an army.
麻萨的士兵早已不存在
The empire... Isn't that Mr. Marse's country?
帝国…不就是马尔斯先生的国家吗
You actually remember.
亏你还记得
Of course I remember.
这种事我当然记得
The largest country ever founded by the human race,
人类建立的最大国家
the Gisaras Empire,
帝国基萨拉斯
is joining hands with many countries
正与许多国家联手
to expand its territory.
不断扩大自己的版图
Was the old man from earlier...
这么说 刚才的大叔是…
The First Prince of Gisaras,
基萨拉斯的第一皇子
Marse's older brother.
马尔斯的哥哥
The Undefeated General, Prince Sluder Gisaras.
不败将军 斯琉达·基萨拉斯
He's the one in charge of executing the emperor's orders.
付诸实行皇帝命令的人就是他
We got away for being one of the Ring Kingdoms,
虽然我们是戒之国 逃过一劫
but he is the conqueror who has seized many countries.
但他是并吞许多国家的实力者
Is the empire actually the bad guy?
帝国其实是很坏的国家吗
Isn't that obvious?
那还用问吗
This is command and invade.
这是支配和侵略
They claim it was to protect us from the Abyssal Creatures,
保护我们远离深渊的魔物
but that was just an excuse.
只不过是借口
Some share that idea,
虽然也有人抱持这种看法
but it's the truth that they united everyone
但他们为了阻止深渊王复活
to prevent the resurrection of the Abyss King.
让人们团结一致也是事实吧
You're very knowledgeable.
你知道得真多呢
Are you impressed?
对我刮目相看了吗
What can a beast possibly know?
区区一只野兽知道什么啊
Cursed woman...
臭女人
I'm going to crush you and mix your remains with the cat powder!
我要把你捣碎 跟木天蓼混在一起烧
This must be the palace.
这里就是王宫吗
What was that?
怎么了
Monsters are attacking.
魔物来袭了
Another prediction came true.
又被那家伙料中了吗
Aren't you worried?
不要紧吗
The empire's soldiers are here to defend us.
帝国军就是为此镇守在这里
Satou, watch out!
佐藤 小心点
Wha...
什…
Impossible!
怎么可能
How can it be here?
为什么会出现在这种地方
Ring King!
戒王
That was too close.
好险
That's the power of the rings...
这就是戒指的力量
-Thank goodness you're all right. -Ring King Satou.
-幸好你没事 -戒王佐藤
-We managed to stay alive. -If he...
-捡回一条命 -如果是他…
I expected nothing less from my husband.
不愧是我丈夫
The legends aren't just fairy tales.
传说并不只是单纯的童话故事吗
So, this is the Ring King.
他就是戒王吗
Yes, Father.
没错 父皇
He is now my husband.
他就是妾身的丈夫
The Ring of Water is his now.
水之戒已经变成他的东西
Hold on.
等等
It seemed you wanted to keep me here
你似乎是想把我关在王宫
so I couldn't hand over the ring.
不让我交出戒指
I thwarted your plan.
但你的计划已经泡汤了
Keeping you here?
关住你?
What are you talking about?
我不懂你在说什么
Cursed vixen.
狐狸精
The army of monsters is approaching.
魔物大军已经逼近这里
Please don't act on your own.
请您不要再擅自行动
Things just got a lot more complicated.
不过这下子事情麻烦了
Right?
对吧
As you predicted,
如同你的预言
the Ring King now has the ring!
戒指已经被交到戒王手上
That means my kingdom will face an even greater calamity!
也就是说 朕的国家将会发生更大的灾难吗
Ring King!
戒王
Why did you have to come here?
要是你没来这里就好了
How is it my fault?
怪我?
Oh my, we wouldn't want your body to take a toll.
哎呀 再这样下去有碍龙体
Let's move you somewhere so you can rest.
我带您到别处休息吧
Curse you, Ring King!
可恶的戒王
Is that sketchy woman your mother, Saphir?
那个可疑的女人是你妈妈吗
Does it look that way?
怎么可能
She is a seer the palace has hired.
她是王宫雇用的占卜师
At some point,
父皇不知道从什么时候
my father grew very dependent on her
就开始事事仰赖她
and became the husk he is now.
变成那副模样
To think my father was once known as the Virtuous King.
以前被誉为贤王的父皇竟然…
Big Sister!
皇姐
Why?
为什么
We swore we'd decide
我们姐妹不是发誓要一起决定
who should be the Ring Princess together!
由谁来完成戒指公主的使命吗
Sorry, but I've made the decision.
抱歉 妾身自己决定了
How could you?
怎么会
She just called you big sister.
她叫你"皇姐"…
Yeah.
嗯
She is my twin sister,
她是妾身的双胞胎妹妹
Saphira.
瑟菲菈
A twin princess?
双胞胎公主
Why did you do it, Saphir?
为什么 瑟菲珞皇姐
Why?
为什么
Why did you marry that mediocre-looking guy?
你要嫁给长相这么平凡的男人
Ouch...
打击
You could've married someone better.
皇姐明明能和更棒的男人结婚
Did you do it for me?
难道是为了保护我吗
How cruel!
好残酷
Destiny has been so cruel to us!
命运实在是太残酷了
Excuse me, Princess Saphira,
恕我直言 瑟菲菈殿下
Satou managed to defeat me in combat.
佐藤好歹是曾经击败 我这个火之公主的男人
Well, he's not particularly reliable when it comes to a fight.
作为战士 他的确感觉不太可靠
You are supposed to defend me!
你不是要帮我说话吗
So...
那个…
I'm an elf, so I don't really understand humans' standards for beauty.
我是精灵 不懂人类的美丑
I'd rather not make any comment.
所以不好说什么
Not you too, Nephrites...
连涅芙丽缇丝都这样
Satou...
佐藤他…
Satou is really cool!
佐藤他明明就很帅
Thank you, Hime!
谢谢你 小姬
Whatever.
不管怎样
She wasn't listening.
根本没在听
You don't have to marry the Ring King now.
你现在已经不需要和戒王结婚了
It's no longer your concern.
不用在意任何事
Sister...
皇姐…
Princess Saphira!
瑟菲菈公主
What is it? The atmosphere got too tense.
怎么了 气氛好像怪怪的
I know everything I say at this point
事到如今 我知道不管说什么
will sound like an excuse to you,
听起来都像是借口
but I've never forgotten our promise.
但我并没有忘记那个约定
I don't want to hear
我不想再听到…
your voice any more.
你的声音了
Princess Saphira!
瑟菲菈公主
You're still as worthless as ever, Marse.
你还是一样没用呢 马尔斯
Mr. Marse has always
马尔斯先生
wanted to come here.
他很早之前就一直想来这个国家
Could it be...
难道是…
That man was Saphira's lover.
他和瑟菲菈是两情相悦的恋人
ROMANCE!?
(爱情罗曼史)
Did you know nothing?
你们什么都没听说吗
It does seem like something he'd do.
真像那个男人会做的事
I'll tell you the story
那就让妾身告诉你们吧
about Maasa and their empire,
关于我们麻萨与他的国家
the Gisaras Empire.
帝国基萨拉斯之间的关系
In the past, the Gisaras Empire
过去 帝国基萨拉斯
wasn't satisfied with conquering the lands of humans.
光是占有人类的领地还不满足
They went as far as
甚至打算
invading the Kingdom of Water, Maasa.
侵略水之国麻萨这块土地
But no battle ever broke out.
可是两国连小战争都没发生
The empire knew it couldn't take Maasa by force,
明白自己动不了麻萨的帝国
so it hoped to strengthen the diplomatic ties.
接着开始希望促进两国交流
I am the Second Prince of the Gisaras Empire,
我是帝国第二皇子
Marmarugias Gisaras.
马尔玛利基亚斯·基萨拉斯
We'd like to learn from Maasa, which has a long-standing history,
希望能向历史悠久的麻萨学习
and improve the relationship between our countries.
并协助两国促进友好关系
They soon became very close.
他们的感情没多久就变很好
There was no doubt that they loved each other.
他们之间的感情绝无虚假
Or at least I thought so.
至少妾身是这么认为
Even if Marse had an unspeakable mission.
就算马尔斯有个不可告人的使命
Please take me!
你干脆把我拐走吧
Marse's mission
马尔斯的使命
was to deliver confidential information about Maasa to the empire.
就是把麻萨的内部情报泄露给帝国
Please wait for me.
希望你等等我
However, he never did it.
但是他并没有这么做
I'll come for you someday.
总有一天 我一定会来接你
Prince Marse.
马尔斯殿下
I believe you.
我相信你
The empire always deals with those who can't fulfil their missions.
可是皇帝不会对派不上用场的人 置之不理
Marse was summoned back to the empire.
马尔斯被叫回帝国
Several months later...
过了几个月后
I will become the Ring King, as per the emperor's order.
我会奉皇帝之命 成为戒王
Then, I can finally marry you.
这样我就能去迎娶你了
Despite it being a twisted marriage to fulfil the Ring King's duty,
就算是配合戒王使命的扭曲婚姻
she had the chance to marry the one she loved.
她还是能与喜欢的对象结婚
We were born to become Ring Princesses.
这对生为戒指公主的我们而言
That was a fate too luxurious to even think about.
简直是不敢奢望的好运
In the end,
结果
Prince Marse gave up on becoming the Ring King.
马尔斯皇子却放弃了戒王的身份
He let a stranger from another world
把戒指交给从异界出现
take the ring.
来路不明的男人
He broke his promise to Saphira.
那家伙违背了和瑟菲菈的誓言
Princess Saphira!
瑟菲菈公主
Please hear me out!
拜托你再听我说一次
My love for you has never changed!
我的心意从那天起完全没变过
I've always loved you!
我一直心系于你
So why?
那为什么
Why didn't you become the Ring King?
为什么你没有成为戒王呢
That's because...
那是因为…
I didn't think
我觉得…
I was worthy.
自己没有资格当
I can't understand what's going on in your mind.
我已经搞不懂你的想法了
The seer showed up afterwards.
那个占卜师就是在那之后现身的
At first, no one believed her.
一开始根本没人相信她
Not until her prediction came true.
直到她的预言成真
To fend off the monsters,
想赶走魔物
the seer's predictions will come in handy.
那个占卜师的预言能派上用场
So, Father kept her here.
于是父皇把她留在身边
That was how he became the way he is now.
现在才会变成那副模样
Do you think the seer was sent here by the empire?
你认为那个占卜师是帝国派来的吗
There must be a connection between them.
他们之间应该有关联
It's exactly why I want to
就是因为这么想
catch that vixen and expose her true nature.
妾身才想抓住那个狐狸精的尾巴
Cursed Saphir.
可恶的瑟菲珞
She ruined my plan.
被她摆了一道
Kill the Ring King and get the rings.
杀了戒王 抢走戒指
For the glory of our great king!
一切都是为了我们伟大的王
Yes!
是
Now I envy him.
真令人羡…
No, this is indecent.
不 真是没节操
Hold on. One of them is missing.
等一下 是不是少了一个人
The catfolk woman...
那个猫人族的…
An attack while everyone is fast asleep.
竟然真的趁熟睡的时候来袭
The Ring Princess of Water was right, after all.
水之公主的预感真准
No horns.
头上没有角
Are these normal humans?
只是普通的人类吗
I knew it. The empire sent them.
果然是帝国派来的吗
Assassins?
刺客
Correct.
对
So, it was real.
原来真的有啊
By the way, where are we headed now?
话说我们现在要去哪里
To get basked in sunlight.
要去晒太阳
The dragon-kins can't regulate their body temperature.
龙人族没办法调节体温
They become slow
只要体温下降
when the body temperature drops.
身体的动作就会变迟钝
I see.
原来如此
That's why she came here right after waking up.
所以才会一起床就来晒太阳
She's trying to warm her body.
让身体变暖吗
When the temperature gets too high, they cool down with water.
然后体温升得太高 就用水来降温
Aren't you going to join them, Granart?
你不去跟她们一起玩吗
I'll take a pass today.
我就不必了
More importantly,
比起这个
I said you were unreliable as a warrior,
虽然我说过你作为战士不太可靠
but you have a good figure.
没想到你的身材这么好
It makes me want to have a baby with you, Satou.
让我很想跟你生孩子 佐藤
Well? How about we do it tonight?
今晚就来做吧 怎么样
No, wait...
不 那个
You can't be the first...
都说了有先来后到
That's Princess Krystal's wishful thinking.
那是克莉丝朵公主自己在讲吧
Hey! What are you doing there?
你们两个在干嘛
I should be the first.
我排第一个
Your waiting love is too weak.
光是等待的爱太弱了
My love for Satou is very passionate.
我对佐藤的爱可是很强烈的
I don't mind getting in the line.
我当第几个都没关系
Hold on!
等一下
A bunch of fools!
真是一群傻瓜呢
"TIGHT" Saphir, that swimsuit...
(紧绷) 瑟…瑟菲珞 那件泳装是…
This is my backyard.
这里是妾身的庭院
I usually walk around naked.
平常我都是裸体
I only put this on because of you.
这是顾虑你们才穿的
By the way, if you're so concerned about
话说回来 你们几个
who gets to do it first,
如果这么在意顺序
why not have a contest?
只要比赛决定不就好了
For example,
比方说
the first to swim over there wins.
最快游到那里的人获胜之类的
Huh?
什么
Meow.
喵
Are you afraid of water?
你该不会怕水吧
Eat this!
看我的
-A bunch of utter fools. -Get this!
-果然是一群傻瓜 -接招吧
-Stop! I hate water!
-住手 我讨厌进水
Erm, I want to...
那个 我也想…
By the way, Satou,
话说回来 佐藤
the seer hasn't given up her plan yet.
那个占卜师应该还没放弃
Stay vigilant even if you're pretending
即使像这样假装大意
to let your guard down.
也要好好提高警觉哦
Wait, this is just an act?
原来只是做做样子啊
A great opportunity to expose that seer.
这是抓住那家伙尾巴的好机会
Do not miss it.
千万别错过了
Mr. Marse.
马尔斯先生
You're in a pretty tough position.
你的处境好像很为难
I can say the same to you.
你也是
It's somewhat my fault that Maasa became
麻萨会变成这样
the way it is now.
有一半是我的责任
I feel like I've failed them.
我觉得很对不起他们
Why did you let me become the Ring King?
为什么你要把戒王的身份让给我呢
If you hadn't,
如果没有让给我
you could've married Princess Saphira.
你就能和瑟菲菈小姐在一起了
It was a burden that was too heavy for me.
我觉得那个责任太沉重了
That's all.
只是这样而已
Is that all?
真的只有这样而已吗
If you have a reason to become the Ring King,
既然有这么重要的理由
you can take the rings for yourself.
你可以从我手上抢走啊
She reminded me of her.
因为我联想到了
The look on Princess Krystal's face reminded me of Saphira.
当时克莉丝朵公主的表情 让我联想到瑟菲菈
She was reunited with her lover.
她和真心所爱的人再次相会了
Knowing how she felt,
既然明白这种心情
I couldn't let myself get in the way.
我怎么可能妨碍你们呢
It's my flaw
不顾一切达成自己的心愿
for not taking what I want by any means necessary.
做不到这件事就是我的缺点
I don't blame Father for calling me worthless.
也难怪父亲会说我没用
But you abandoned everything for Princess Krystal's sake.
但是你为了克莉丝朵公主 抛下所有一切
You are more worthy of becoming the Ring King
果然还是你这样的人
than I am.
比较适合成为戒王
Brother!
皇兄
Please reconsider!
能不能再重新考虑一下呢
We agreed not to intervene in Maasa.
当初不是说好不会干涉麻萨吗
It's Father's order to send reinforcements here.
派援军到水之国是皇帝的旨意
You haven't been forgiven
你违反命令 没有成为戒王的罪
for going against the order and not becoming the Ring King.
还没得到原谅
But you've done your part to earn the Ring King's trust.
但你现在努力得到戒王的信任
We know their plan.
让我们知道他的动向
Father considers that your redemption.
父皇把它当成是将功补过
You must answer Father's expectations, Marse.
你要回应父皇的期待 马尔斯
The Gisaras Empire is the only place
除了帝国基萨拉斯以外
you can return to.
你没有其他能回去的地方
What do you want?
找我有什么事
Take the ring, Prince Marse.
把戒指抢过来 马尔斯王子
Don't be ridiculous.
你在胡说什么
That is the emperor's order!
这是皇帝陛下的旨意
You've earned the Ring King's trust
要你得到戒王的信任
for this very purpose.
为了就是这一刻
Three days from now, an army of monsters will attack Maasa.
三天后 魔物大军会攻击麻萨
Make use of the chaos and kill the Ring King.
你就在那场战斗中趁乱杀了戒王